[
  {
    "front": "Piada (ğŸ˜‚)",
    "back": "grap",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Grama (ğŸŒ±)",
    "back": "gras",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Grosso, rude (ğŸªµ)",
    "back": "grof",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Galo (ğŸ“)",
    "back": "haan",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Ela, sua (ğŸ‘©)",
    "back": "haar",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Metade (Â½)",
    "back": "half",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "MÃ£o (âœ‹)",
    "back": "hand",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Duro, forte (ğŸ’ª)",
    "back": "hard",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "CoraÃ§Ã£o (â¤ï¸)",
    "back": "hart",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Muito, inteiro (ğŸŒ•)",
    "back": "heel",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Quente (ğŸ”¥)",
    "back": "heet",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Ajudar (ğŸ†˜)",
    "back": "help",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Cervo (ğŸ¦Œ)",
    "back": "hert",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Aqui (ğŸ“)",
    "back": "hier",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "ChapÃ©u (ğŸ©)",
    "back": "hoed",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Canto, Ã¢ngulo (ğŸ“)",
    "back": "hoek",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "CÃ£o (ğŸ•)",
    "back": "hond",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Alto, elevado (â›°ï¸)",
    "back": "hoog",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "EsperanÃ§a (ğŸŒˆ)",
    "back": "hoop",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  },
  {
    "front": "Casa (ğŸ )",
    "back": "huis",
    "fsrsCard": {
      "due": "2025-10-22T19:30:00.803Z",
      "stability": 0,
      "difficulty": 0,
      "elapsed_days": 0,
      "scheduled_days": 0,
      "reps": 0,
      "lapses": 0,
      "state": 0
    }
  }
]